<?xml version="1.0"?><books>   <book id="xmlApps">      <title>XML Applications</title>      <isbn>1-861001-52-5</isbn>      <authors>         <author>            <first_name>Frank</first_name>            <last_name>Boumphrey</last_name>         </author>         <author>            <first_name>Stephen</first_name>            <last_name>Mohr</last_name>         </author>         <author>            <first_name>Paul</first_name>            <last_name>Houle</last_name>         </author>      </authors>      <description>Mastering XML is certainly difficult, but XML Applications provides all the background you'll need to get started. Early sections outline why XML is a better way to deliver Internet content. The authors look at available XML tools (including freeware utilities and the Internet Explorer 5 beta) and XML basics, such as Document Type Definitions (DTDs), cascading style sheets (CSS), and Extensible Stylesheet Language (XSL). The authors also present real-world implementations of XML, including Microsoft's Channel Definition Format and the Chemical Markup Language (for chemists).</description>      <publication>Book</publication>      <coverURL>1525.gif</coverURL>      <URL>http://webdev.wrox.co.uk/books/1525/</URL>      <keywords>         <keyword>XML</keyword>         <keyword>XSL</keyword>         <keyword>DTD</keyword>      </keywords>   </book>   <book id="DDA">      <title>Designing Distributed Applications</title>      <isbn>1-861002-27-0</isbn>      <authors>         <author>            <first_name>Stephen</first_name>            <last_name>Mohr</last_name>         </author>      </authors>      <description>Designing Distributed Applications is all about creating Cooperative Network Applications. Their aim is to promote the re-use of Intranet and Internet applications and maintain the viability of applications in the face of change.</description>      <publication>Book</publication>      <coverURL>2270.gif</coverURL>      <URL>http://webdev.wrox.co.uk/books/2270/</URL>      <keywords>         <keyword>XML</keyword>         <keyword>ASP</keyword>         <keyword>IE5</keyword>      </keywords>   </book>   <book id="untitled">      <title></title>      <isbn>1-81001-65-7</isbn>      <authors>         <author>            <first_name>Frank</first_name>            <last_name>Boumphrey</last_name>         </author>      </authors>      <description>Here's a book for those already proficient in using HTML to design more complex Web pages. Its purpose is to educate the reader on using style sheets and XML to make better Web pages. Style sheets are a means of providing additional and advanced specifications for the translation of mark-up codes. As a result, designers can present more advanced designs while actually reducing coding, increasing the legibility of marked-up copy, and creating a page that's easier to maintain. They can be used with the Web's workhorse markup language, HTML, or with the newer, more advanced XML.</description>      <publication>Book</publication>      <coverURL>1657.gif</coverURL>      <URL>http://webdev.wrox.co.uk/books/1657/</URL>      <keywords>         <keyword>Style</keyword>         <keyword>Sheets</keyword>         <keyword>CSS</keyword>      </keywords>   </book>   <book id="xmlDI">      <title>XML Design and Implementation</title>      <isbn>1-861002-28-9</isbn>      <authors>         <author>            <first_name>Paul</first_name>            <last_name>Spencer</last_name>         </author>      </authors>      <description>XML is a mark up language which allows you to define your own tags, and to define data rather than format it. The overall concepts of XML are quite well understood but there is little information available about issues of developing applications using XML. By considering the decisions to be made at various stages of the project, it will help readers understand the various aspects of XML and its related technologies. It will stress the benefits of XML in informational systems, where it can be used to separate content from presentation, and in transactional systems, where it can act as a low-cost alternative to EDI protocols.</description>      <publication>Book</publication>      <coverURL>2289.gif</coverURL>      <URL>http://webdev.wrox.co.uk/books/2289/</URL>      <keywords>         <keyword>XML</keyword>         <keyword>XSL</keyword>         <keyword>ASP</keyword>         <keyword>Design</keyword>         <keyword>Implementation</keyword>      </keywords>   </book>   <book id="xmlIE5ref">      <title>XML IE5 Programmer's Reference</title>      <isbn>1-861001-57-6</isbn>      <authors>         <author>            <first_name>Alex</first_name>            <last_name>Homer</last_name>         </author>      </authors>      <description>A handy and straightforward owner's manual to XML, XML in IE5 Programmer's Reference surveys the current state of XML as it applies to Microsoft Internet Explorer 5 and provides an excellent introduction to the many composite aspects of XML.</description>      <publication>Book</publication>      <coverURL>1576.gif</coverURL>      <URL>http://webdev.wrox.co.uk/books/1576/</URL>      <keywords>         <keyword>XML</keyword>         <keyword>IE5</keyword>         <keyword>XSL</keyword>      </keywords>   </book>   <book id="begAsp">      <title>Beginning ASP</title>      <isbn>1-861001-34-7</isbn>      <authors>         <author>            <first_name>Brian</first_name>            <last_name>Francis</last_name>         </author>         <author>            <first_name>Juan</first_name>            <last_name>Llibre</last_name>         </author>         <author>            <first_name>John</first_name>            <last_name>Kauffman</last_name>         </author>      </authors>      <description>If you're new to Web development--or even new to programming in general--Beginning Active Server Pages 2.0 is good place to start for learning how to program with Active Server Pages (ASPs) using Microsoft Internet Information Server (IIS). In this accessible and clearly written text, the authors do a fine job of presenting the basics of using ASPs in digestible increments, including how to program with databases.</description>      <publication>Book</publication>      <coverURL>1347.gif</coverURL>      <URL>http://webdev.wrox.co.uk/books/1347</URL>      <keywords>         <keyword>ASP</keyword>         <keyword>2.0</keyword>      </keywords>   </book>   <book id="ado2Ref">      <title>ADO 2.0 Programmer's Reference</title>      <isbn>1-861001-83-5</isbn>      <authors>         <author>            <first_name>Dave</first_name>            <last_name>Sussman</last_name>         </author>         <author>            <first_name>Alex</first_name>            <last_name>Homer</last_name>         </author>      </authors>      <description>Microsoft's new ActiveX Data Object (ADO) 2 standard for database access allows programs to access traditional databases just as easily as other types of data (such as Web pages and spreadsheets). The ADO 2.0 Programmer's Reference gets you up and running with the new ADO and includes a full reference to its objects and methods.</description>      <publication>Book</publication>      <coverURL>1835.gif</coverURL>      <URL>http://webdev.wrox.co.uk/books/1835/</URL>      <keywords>         <keyword>ADO</keyword>         <keyword>Data</keyword>         <keyword>2.0</keyword>      </keywords>   </book>   <book id="asp2">      <title>Professional ASP 2.0</title>      <isbn>1-861001-26-6</isbn>      <authors>         <author>            <first_name>Alex</first_name>            <last_name>Fedorov</last_name>         </author>         <author>            <first_name>Dave</first_name>            <last_name>Sussman</last_name>         </author>         <author>            <first_name>Brian</first_name>            <last_name>Francis</last_name>         </author>      </authors>      <description>The book discusses the Internet in terms of the history of client/server systems and describes why it is a better way to deliver scaleable, maintainable systems using thin clients. It describes basic Microsoft tools, such as NT4, Internet Information Server (IIS), and Personal Web Server. The authors then move toward the basics of using Active Server Pages (ASPs) starting with basic objects (such as the Request, Cookies, and Response objects). They stress a solutions-basic approach with plenty of examples to show what's going on. Sections on Active Server Components and listings of third-party controls that can enhance your ASP Web site are particularly useful.</description>      <publication>Book</publication>      <coverURL>1266.gif</coverURL>      <URL>http://webdev.wrox.co.uk/books/1266/</URL>      <keywords>         <keyword>ASP</keyword>         <keyword>2.0</keyword>      </keywords>   </book>   <book id="aspTech">      <title>Professional ASP Techniques For Webmasters</title>      <isbn>1-861001-79-7</isbn>      <authors>         <author>            <first_name>Alex</first_name>            <last_name>Homer</last_name>         </author>      </authors>      <description>Professional ASP Techniques for Webmasters sits right at the center of the web application information space, on both the strategic and tactical levels, and will save its purchasers from hours of painful struggle and experimentation. The major sections describe dynamic web page generation, site navigation, browser compatibility, remote administration, and gathering information and creating reports about site visitors. A final "plug and play" chapter includes a number of tricks and traps that didn't fit in logically elsewhere, ranging from the creation of pop-up windows to configuring the IIS SMTP service. The book is supplemented with downloads, errata, and feedback forms on the WROX web site.</description>      <publication></publication>      <coverURL>1797.gif</coverURL>      <URL>http://webdev.wrox.co.uk/books/1797/</URL>      <keywords>         <keyword>ASP</keyword>         <keyword>2.0</keyword>         <keyword>Techniques</keyword>      </keywords>   </book>   <book id="mtsMsmq">      <title>Professional MTS MSMQ</title>      <isbn>1-861001-46-0</isbn>      <authors>         <author>            <first_name>David</first_name>            <last_name>Sussman</last_name>         </author>         <author>            <first_name>Alex</first_name>            <last_name>Homer</last_name>         </author>      </authors>      <description>If you're thinking of powering your next Web site with the latest in Microsoft Internet technologies, and you program in Visual Basic (VB), then Professional MTS and MSMQ with VB and ASP is for you. This fast-paced tutorial gives you a crash course in using Microsoft Transaction Server (MTS) and the new Microsoft Message Queue (MSMQ) Server, along with other Microsoft tools, for creating dynamic, commerce-enabled Web sites and Web-based applications. The authors provide a step-by-step guide to configuring and designing with VBScript, active server pages (ASPs) using transactions, and the new capabilities of message queuing (which permits systems to be designed with fault tolerance in mind.) Readable and to the point, this guide will likely be all you need for getting the basics of the best in designing Web sites using Microsoft's latest Web tools.</description>      <publication>Book</publication>      <coverURL>1460.gif</coverURL>      <URL>http://webdev.wrox.co.uk/books/1460/</URL>      <keywords>         <keyword>ASP</keyword>         <keyword>MTS</keyword>         <keyword>MSMQ</keyword>      </keywords>   </book>   <book id="ie4Prog">      <title>Professional IE4 Programming</title>      <isbn>1-861000-70-7</isbn>      <authors>         <author>            <first_name>Dino</first_name>            <last_name>Esposito</last_name>         </author>         <author>            <first_name>Alex</first_name>            <last_name>Homer</last_name>         </author>      </authors>      <description>For readers who want to make their Web pages more interactive, dynamic and useful, this book offers practical advanced techniques and detailed examples, covers dynamic new Web components and adds a whole new concept to creating exciting and dynamic Web pages.</description>      <publication>Book</publication>      <coverURL>0707.gif</coverURL>      <URL>http://webdev.wrox.co.uk/books/0707/</URL>      <keywords>         <keyword>IE4</keyword>         <keyword>Programming</keyword>         <keyword>Explorer</keyword>      </keywords>   </book>   <book id="ie5Dhtml">      <title>IE5 DHTML</title>      <isbn>1-861001-74-6</isbn>      <authors>         <author>            <first_name>Brian</first_name>            <last_name>Francis</last_name>         </author>         <author>            <first_name>Alex</first_name>            <last_name>Homer</last_name>         </author>         <author>            <first_name>Chris</first_name>            <last_name>Ullman</last_name>         </author>      </authors>      <description>This Wrox Programmer's Reference provides a basic introduction to Dynamic HTML. This includes showing how it relates to existing technologies, including the latest CSS2 version of style sheets, which provide the basis for DHTML. Examples are presented in both VBScript and JavaScript and there is ample coverage of techniques for working with text, tables, windows, forms and filters. As in the previous edition, there are also extensive reference sections on Dynamic HTML, VBScript, and JavaScript.</description>      <publication>Book</publication>      <coverURL>1746.gif</coverURL>      <URL>http://webdev.wrox.co.uk/books/1746/</URL>      <keywords>         <keyword>IE5</keyword>         <keyword>DHTML</keyword>         <keyword>Dynamic</keyword>      </keywords>   </book>   <book id="siteServ">      <title>Site Server Personalization and Membership</title>      <isbn>1-861001-94-0</isbn>      <authors>         <author>            <first_name>Rob</first_name>            <last_name>Howard</last_name>         </author>      </authors>      <description>This book focuses on the Personalization and Membership capabilities of Site Server 3.0, which enable you to do clever things like this: ISP - Use Personalization and Membership to personalize IIS administrative tool using the existing IIS web administration interface, to allow different members to have different administrative privileges; also, to implement user membership on various levels to provide simple display and access privileges as well as integrating with existing applications. Interactive Web Site - Use Personalization and Membership to control the display of the content on a site, thus giving end-users a richer browsing experience. This example theme demonstrates how to incorporate lightweight samples and ideas into their existing web site. Intranet - Use Personalization and Membership in an Intranet site to control access to items on the network. This would be a higher end example of the type of things that Personalization and Membership can do.</description>      <publication>Book</publication>      <coverURL>1940.gif</coverURL>      <URL>http://webdev.wrox.co.uk/books/1940/</URL>      <keywords>         <keyword>SiteServer</keyword>         <keyword>Site</keyword>         <keyword>Server</keyword>      </keywords>   </book>   <book id="aspRef">      <title>ASP 2.0 Programmer's Reference</title>      <isbn>1-81002-45-9</isbn>      <authors>         <author>            <first_name>Dave</first_name>            <last_name>Sussman</last_name>         </author>         <author>            <first_name>Alex</first_name>            <last_name>Homer</last_name>         </author>      </authors>      <description>ASP (Active Server Pages) is a Microsoft technology that provides a framework for developers to construct dynamic Web pages. These pages can interact with custom-built components or databases to produce solid and interesting Internet/intranet sites and Web-based applications. A succinct and eminently portable book, ASP 2.0 Programmer's Reference is a resource Internet/intranet developers will find they use again and again.</description>      <publication>Book</publication>      <coverURL>2459.gif</coverURL>      <URL>http://webdev.wrox.co.uk/books/2459</URL>      <keywords>         <keyword>ASP</keyword>         <keyword>Active Server Pages</keyword>      </keywords>   </book></books>